Guide to the Robert Penn Warren Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1922-88; Series I; 40; (95 boxes)
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
    - Forgotson, E. S., 1946-75 (Box 26, Folder 503)
    - Forum, 1975-79 (Box 26, Folder 504)
    - Foster, Charles H., 1949-86 (Box 26, Folder 505-08)
    - Four Quarters, 1960-76 (Box 26, Folder 509)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, 1941-68 (Box 26, Folder 510)
    - Frankel, Aaron, 1954-68 (Box 26, Folder 511-12)
    - Franklin and Marshall College, 1959-61 (Box 26, Folder 513)
    - Franklin Library, 1974-85 (Box 26, Folder 514-16)
    - Frasier, Jerry, 1980-81 (Box 27, Folder 517)
    - Freund, Gerald, 1967-85 (Box 27, Folder 518)
      See also: MacArthur Foundation, Box 43, folder 819
    - Fridy, Will, 1973-81 (Box 27, Folder 519)
      See also: Western Kentucky University, Box 78, folder 1529
    - Friedlander, Marc
      See: University of North Carolina (Greensboro), Box 51, folder 1021
    - Friedman, J. Roger, 1974-75 (Box 27, Folder 520)
    - Frost, Kenneth, 1975-76 (Box 27, Folder 521)
    - Furioso
      See: Howard Nemerov, Box 49, folder 972
    - Furnas, J. C., 1956-59 (Box 27, Folder 522)
    - "G" general, 1941-86 (Box 27, Folder 523-27)
    - Galantiere, Lewis, 1959-76 (Box 28, Folder 528)
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth Galbraith, Kitty, 1972-86 (Box 28, Folder 529)
    - Gallup, Donald
    - Garber, Robert D., 1977 (Box 28, Folder 530)
    - Gardner, Burdett, 1950-64 (Box 28, Folder 531)
    - Gardner, Isabella (Mrs. Allen Tate), 1974-79, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 532)
    - Garwick, Geoff, 1968-71 (Box 28, Folder 533)
    - Gay, Peter, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 534)
    - Georgetown University, 1961-86 (Box 28, Folder 535)
    - Georgia Institute of Technology, 1967-68 (Box 28, Folder 536)
    - Georgia Review, 1974-85 (Box 28, Folder 537-39)
    - Georgia, University of, Press, 1968-85 (Box 28, Folder 540)
    - Gerber, Philip, 1973-84 (Box 28, Folder 541)
    - Gibson, Richard, 1950-51 (Box 28, Folder 542)
    - Gill, Brendan, 1960, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 543)
    - Girault, Norton, 1944-86 (Box 28, Folder 544-46)
    - Glickman, James, 1979-83 (Box 28, Folder 547)
    - Goldberg, Dorothy (Mrs. Arthur), 1967 (Box 28, Folder 548)
    - Golishev, V., 1972-80 (Box 28, Folder 549)
    - Gonzalez, N. V. M., 1948-60 (Box 29, Folder 550)
    - Gordon, Caroline, 1932-64, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 551)
    - Gorlier, Claudio, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 552)
    - Govan, Thomas Govan, Jane, 1953-61 (Box 29, Folder 553)
    - Grangaard, John, 1971-79, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 554)
    - Gray, James, 1943-52, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 555)
    - Gray, Richard, 1968-81 (Box 29, Folder 556)
    - Green, Paul, 1954-63 (Box 29, Folder 557)
    - Greene, Graham
      See: Eyre and Spottiswoode, Box 91, folder 1718
    - Greenfield Hill Improvement Society, 1964 Dec 8 (Box 29, Folder 558)
    - Grimshaw, James A., 1973-87 (Box 29, Folder 559-61)
    - Grinnell College, 1946-67 (Box 29, Folder 562)
    - Griswold, A. Whitney Griswold, Mary, 1950-63 (Box 29, Folder 563)
    - Guerrieri, Gerardo Guerrieri, Anne, 1955-61 (Box 29, Folder 564)
    - Guggenheim, John Simon, Memorial Foundation, 1934-83 (Box 29, Folder 565)
    - Guicharnaud, Jacques, 1962-78, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 566)
    - Guthrie, A. B., 1949-50 (Box 29, Folder 567)
    - Guthrie, Bill, 1952-55 (Box 29, Folder 568)
    - Guy, William, 1968-74 (Box 29, Folder 569)
    - "H" general, 1940-87 (Box 30, Folder 570-81)
    - Hagens, Lucie, 1981-83 (Box 31, Folder 582)
    - Haieff, Alexei, 1970-80 (Box 31, Folder 583)
    - Haight, Gordon S., 1950-75 (Box 31, Folder 584)
    - Halberstam, David, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 585)
    - Hall, Adrian
      See: Trinity Square Repertory Theatre, Box 71, folder 1408
    - Hall, James B., 1952-61 (Box 31, Folder 586)
    - Halpern, David
      See: Antaeus, Box 4, folder 64
    - Halverson, Marvin Pierce, 1961-65 (Box 31, Folder 587)
    - Hamilton, Fowler, 1973-83 (Box 31, Folder 588)
    - Hamilton, Ian, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 589)
    - Hammerstein, Oscar, 1960 Apr 21 (Box 31, Folder 590)
    - Harper and Row, Publishers (Harper and Brothers), 1932-68 (Box 31, Folder 591)
    - Harper's Bazaar, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 592)
    - Harper's Magazine, 1945-77 (Box 31, Folder 593)
    - Harrington, Evans
      See: University of Mississippi, Box 46, folder 900 and Southern Literary Festival Association
    - Hartford, University of, 1968-82 (Box 31, Folder 594)
    - Harvard Advocate, 1965-77 (Box 31, Folder 595)
    - Harvard Educational Review, 1960-76 (Box 31, Folder 596)
    - Harvard University, 1948-85 (Box 31, Folder 597-601)
    - Harvard University Press, 1964-83 (Box 32, Folder 602-03)
    - Haverford College, 1948-78 (Box 32, Folder 604)
    - Havird, David, 1974-86 (Box 32, Folder 605)
    - Hawaii, University of, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 606)
    - Hawkins, John R., 1980-85 (Box 32, Folder 607)
    - Hayakawa, S. J.
      See: U.S. English, Box 72, folder 1429
    - Haydn, Hiram, 1958-63 (Box 32, Folder 608)
      See: American Scholar and Atheneum Publishers, Box 5, folder 77
    - Hayo, Samuel
      See: International Poetry Forum, Box 34, folder 666
    - Hazzard, Shirley
      See: Shirley Steegmuller, Box 66, folder 1314
    - Heard, Jean Heard, Alexander, 1975-84 (Box 32, Folder 609)
    - Hecht, Anthony, 1980-86 (Box 32, Folder 610)
    - Hecht, Roger, 1964-68 (Box 32, Folder 611)
    - Heilman, Robert B., 1944-86, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 612-14)
      See also: University of Washington, Box 76, folder 1497
    - Hellman, Lillian, 1957-77 (Box 32, Folder 615)
    - Henn, T. R., 1965-66 (Box 32, Folder 616)
    - Hersey, John, 1947-86 (Box 32, Folder 617-18)
    - Herzfelder, Richard, 1977, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 619)
    - Heustis Supply Company, 1964 Apr 4 (Box 32, Folder 620)
    - Heyen, William, 1973-84 (Box 32, Folder 621)
    - Hicks, Granville, 1947, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 622)
    - Hicks, Helsey M., 1963-64 (Box 32, Folder 623)
    - Highet, Gilbert, 1940, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 624)
    - The Hill School, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 625)
    - Hilles, Frederick W., 1951-74 (Box 32, Folder 626)
    - Hilliard, Louise, 1951-55 (Box 32, Folder 627)
    - Hills, Rust
      See: Esquire, Box 24, folder 458
    - Himmersky, Krassim
    - Hitchcock, Reynald
      See: Albert Erskine, Box 24, folder 457
    - Hivnor, Robert, 1945-86 (Box 32, Folder 628)
    - Hoffman, Daniel, 1965-80 (Box 33, Folder 629-30)
    - Holden, Betty Holden, Reuben A., 1966-84 (Box 33, Folder 631)
      See also: Warren Wilson College and Yale University (general), Box 84, folder 1645
    - Holiday Magazine, 1957-64 (Box 33, Folder 632)
    - Holland, Kenneth, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 633)
    - Hollander, John, 1966-77 (Box 33, Folder 634-35)
    - Holt, Theodore
      See: Corporation for Public Broadcasting, Box 18, folder 364
    - Holy Cross, College of, 1959-68 (Box 33, Folder 636)
    - Hook, Sidney, 1958-72 (Box 33, Folder 637)
    - Horgan, Paul, 1972-87 (Box 33, Folder 638)
    - Horizon, 1947-71 (Box 33, Folder 639)
    - Hospitalized Veterans' Writing Project, 1957-69 (Box 33, Folder 640)
    - Hound & Horn, 1930-33 (Box 33, Folder 641)
    - Houseman, John, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 642)
    - Housman, Laurence, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 643)
    - Howard, Richard, 1972-85, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 644)
    - Howe, Irving, 1958, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 645)
    - Howes, Barbara, 1965-77 (Box 33, Folder 646)
    - Hudson Group, Inc., 1978 (Box 33, Folder 647)
    - The Hudson Review, 1947-73 (Box 33, Folder 648)
    - Hughes, Lawrence, 1964-79 (Box 33, Folder 649)
    - Humphrey, William, 1957-66 (Box 33, Folder 650)
    - Hunter College, 1974-75 (Box 33, Folder 651)
    - Huntington Hartford Foundation, 1950-59 (Box 33, Folder 652)
    - Hurley, Joseph, 1956-58 (Box 33, Folder 653)
    - Hurt, Henry, 1965-81 (Box 33, Folder 654-55)
    - Hyneman, Charles, 1950-75 (Box 33, Folder 656)
    - Hynes, Samuel, 1947-77, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 657)
    - "I" general, 1948-85 (Box 34, Folder 658-60)
    - Illinois, University of, 1947-89 (Box 34, Folder 661)
    - Illinois, University of, Press, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 662)
    - Indiana University, 1946-72 (Box 34, Folder 663)
    - Institute of Contemporary Arts, 1945-61 (Box 34, Folder 664-65)
    - International P.E.N.
      See: P.E.N., Box 55, folder 1080
    - International Poetry Forum, 1968-77, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 666)
    - Iowa, University of, 1940-83 (Box 34, Folder 667)
    - Ironwood, 1977-78 (Box 34, Folder 668)
    - Iseman, Peter, 1971-73 (Box 34, Folder 669)
    - Israel, Calvin, 1975-81 (Box 34, Folder 670)
    - Ithaca College, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 671)
    - Itofusi, Hiromi, 1983-85 (Box 34, Folder 672)
    - "J" general, 1935-86 (Box 35, Folder 673-75)
    - J. Howard Woolmer, 1980-85 (Box 35, Folder 676)
    - Jackpine Press, 1980-81 (Box 35, Folder 677)
    - James Agee Film Project, 1981-85, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 678)
    - James Madison University, 1984-85 (Box 35, Folder 679)
    - Janeway, Elizabeth, 1956, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 680)
    - Jansson, Marian, 1982-83 (Box 35, Folder 681)
    - Jarrell, Mary, 1865-75 (Box 35, Folder 682)
    - Jarrell, Randall, 1944-65, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 683-84)
    - Jeakins, Dorothy, 1949-85, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 685)
    - Jerrold, Douglas, 1963-64, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 686)
      See also: Eyre and Spottiswoode, Box 91, folder 1718
    - Jesse Stuart Foundation, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 687)
      See also: Harold C. Richardson, Box 59, folder 1174
    - Jessup, John Knox Jessup, Eunice, 1949-69 (Box 35, Folder 688)
    - Jewish Minority Research, 1960-61, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 689)
    - John B. Stetson University, 1948-49 (Box 35, Folder 690)
    - Johns Hopkins University, 1949-85 (Box 35, Folder 691)
    - Johnson, A. Theodore Johnson, Marie, 1944-66 (Box 35, Folder 692)
    - Johnson, Lyndon Baines, 1964-77, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 693)
    - Jordan, Amy Jordan, Ed R., 1951-60 (Box 35, Folder 694)
    - Josephy, Alvin, 1982-86 (Box 35, Folder 695)
    - "K" general, 1941-86 (Box 36, Folder 696-702)
    - Katkov, Norman C. Katkov, Betty, 1952-59 (Box 36, Folder 703)
    - Kaufman, Craig, 1972-86 (Box 36, Folder 704)
    - Kazan, Elia, 1957 Oct 2 (Box 36, Folder 705)
    - Kazin, Alfred, 1942-53 (Box 36, Folder 706)
    - Kehl, D. G., 1964-81 (Box 36, Folder 707)
    - Kellogg, Marjorie, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 708)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1960-64 (Box 37, Folder 709)
    - Kenneth Patchen Fund, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 710)
    - Kent State University, 1959-83 (Box 37, Folder 711)
    - Kentucky Poetry Review, 1978-87 (Box 37, Folder 712)
    - Kentucky, State of, 1977-86, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 713)
    - Kentucky, University of, 1948-85 (Box 37, Folder 714)
    - Kentucky, University of, Libraries, 1950-81 (Box 37, Folder 715-16)
    - Kentucky, University Press of, 1956-84 (Box 37, Folder 717)
    - Kentucky Wesleyan University, 1962-73, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 718)
    - Kenyon College, 1950-78 (Box 37, Folder 719)
    - The Kenyon Review, 1946-79 (Box 37, Folder 720)
      See also: John Crowe Ransom, Box 59 folder 1153, Robb Ransom, and Philip Rice, Box 59, folder 1171
    - Kern, Alexander Kern, Jean, 1941-66, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 721)
    - Kerr, Chester Kerr, Joan, 1974, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 722)
    - Kissinger, Henry
    - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1960-71 (Box 37, Folder 723)
    - King, Morton B., 1956-70 (Box 37, Folder 724)
    - Kinnell, Galway, 1983 Oct 31 (Box 37, Folder 725)
    - Kinney, Arthur, 1964-66 (Box 37, Folder 726)
    - Kirby, Thomas, 1961-76, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 727)
    - Kirstein, George, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 728)
    - Knopf, Alfred
      See: Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., Box 3, folder 35
    - Krämer, Ilse, 1948-53 (Box 37, Folder 729)
    - Kronenberger, Louis, 1968, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 730)
    - Kubie, Lawrence, M.D., 1960-73, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 731)
    - Kuehl, J.R., 1964-65 (Box 37, Folder 732)
    - Kunitz, Stanley, 1960-74, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 733)
    - "L" general, 1941-89 (Box 38, Folder 734-745)
    - Lacy, Dan, 1969-74 (Box 38, Folder 746)
    - Lacy, Sam
      See: McGraw Hill Publishers, Box 43, folder 831
    - Lahr, John H., 1963, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 747)
    - Langner, Lawrence
      See: Theatre Guild, Box 71, folder 1392
    - Lanier, Lyle H., 1951-80 (Box 38, Folder 748)
    - Laughlin, James
      See: New Directions, Box 49, folder 976
    - Lea, Sydney, 1982-84, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 749)
    - Leary, Lewis
      See: Columbia University, Box 18, folder 342
    - LeCompte, Kendall, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 750)
    - Lee, Mark, 1973-86 (Box 39, Folder 751)
    - Leiberman, Larry, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 752)
    - Leiper, Gudger Bart, 1948-55 (Box 39, Folder 753)
    - LeMoyne College, 1973-77 (Box 39, Folder 754)
    - Lerner, Max, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 755)
    - Lessard, Jack, 1956-57 (Box 39, Folder 756)
    - Lesser, Simon O., 1965-73 (Box 39, Folder 757)
    - Lettres Modernes, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 758)
    - Levant, Howard, 1954-79 (Box 39, Folder 759)
    - Levensohn, Alan, 1962-64 (Box 39, Folder 760)
    - Levertov, Denise, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 761)
    - Levin, Harry, 1956-74 (Box 39, Folder 762)
    - Levin, Meyer, 1957, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 763)
    - Lewis, C. S., 1954-55 (Box 39, Folder 764)
    - Lewis, Emma, 1972-85, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 765)
    - Lewis, R. W. B., 1951-83 (Box 39, Folder 766-67)
    - Lewis, Roger, 1985-86 (Box 39, Folder 768)
    - Lewis, Sinclair, 1944-46 (Box 39, Folder 769)
    - Lewiston, Alice
      See: Radiodiffusion Francaise, Box 58, folder 1148
    - Librarie Stock
      See: Editions Stock, Box 23, folder 438
    - Library of Congress
      - Adams, Leonie, 1948-71 (Box 39, Folder 770)
      - Bishop, Elizabeth, 1948-50 (Box 39, Folder 771)
      - Boorstin, Daniel J., 1986 (Box 39, Folder 772)
      - Broderick, John C., 1978-87 (Box 39, Folder 773)
      - Galbraith, Nancy, 1986-87 (Box 39, Folder 774)
      - MacLeish, Archibald, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 775)
    - Library of Congress, 1949
      - General, 1944-69 (Box 40, Folder 776-78)
    - Lieberman, Leo, 1944-69
      See: Carmen Capalbo, Box 14, folder 265
    - Life, 1946-86 (Box 40, Folder 779)
    - Link, Franz H.
      See: Englisches Seminar, Box 23, folder 453
    - Literary Classics of the United States, 1979-82 (Box 40, Folder 780)
    - Literary Guild of America, 1950-83 (Box 40, Folder 781)
    - Littlefield, William Littlefield, William, Jr., 1945-81 (Box 40, Folder 782)
    - Loeb Drama Center
      See: Robert Chapman, Box 15, folder 286
    - Logan, Harlan, 1965-68 (Box 40, Folder 783)
    - Logan, Joshua, 1948-51 (Box 40, Folder 784)
    - Lohner, Edgar, 1950-70, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 785)
    - Longley, John L., 1958-73, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 786)
    - Lord John Press, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 787)
    - Lotos Club, 1963-78 (Box 40, Folder 788)
    - Louisiana State University, 1941-85, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 789)
    - Louisiana State University, Press, 1942-85 (Box 40, Folder 790)
    - University of Louisville, 1948-83 (Box 40, Folder 791)
    - Lowell, Robert, 1946-75 (Box 40, Folder 792-93)
    - Loyola University, 1957-75 (Box 40, Folder 794)
    - Lubasky, Richard, 1968-72 (Box 40, Folder 795)
    - Luce, Henry, [c. 1942] (Box 40, Folder 796)
    - Lytle, Andrew, 1931-86 (Box 41, Folder 797-801)
      See also: Sewanee Review, Box 64, folder 1261
    - "M" general (MacA-Maur), 1933-86 (Box 41, Folder 802-08)
    - "M" general (Maxo-Murr), 1943-87 (Box 42, Folder 809-17)
    - Mabry, Tom Mabry, Ethel Mabry, Eliza, 1951-85, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 818)
    - MacArthur Foundation, 1980-86 (Box 43, Folder 819-20)
    - McCarthy, Cormac, 1981, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 821)
    - McCarthy, Mary, 1942, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 822)
    - MacCauley Company, 1931, 1934 (Box 43, Folder 823)
    - MaClatchy, J. D., 1972-85 (Box 43, Folder 824)
    - McDonald, John McDonald, Dorothy, 1955-74 (Box 43, Folder 825)
    - McDowell, David, 1964-82 (Box 43, Folder 826)
      See: Crown Publishers, Box 19, folder 383
    - McDowell, Tremaine, 1946-59, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 827)
    - McGehee, Edward, 1947 (Box 43, Folder 828)
    - MacGillivray, Arthur S. J., 1962-83 (Box 43, Folder 829)
    - McGovern, George, 1965, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 830)
    - McGraw Hill Book Company, 1951-66 (Box 43, Folder 831)
    - McGuire, John D.
      See: Claremont University Center, Box 17, folder 313
    - McGuire, William, 1984-86 (Box 43, Folder 832)
    - Mack, Maynard, 1960-78 (Box 43, Folder 833)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1944-79 (Box 43, Folder 834)
    - McLuhan, Marshall, 1946 Dec 17 (Box 43, Folder 835)
    - McMahon, Tom, 1951-67 (Box 43, Folder 836)
    - McMains, Charles, 1984-85 (Box 43, Folder 837)
    - MacMillan Publishing Company, 1947-83 (Box 43, Folder 838)
    - McNamee, Tom, 1968-87 (Box 44, Folder 839-41)
    - McNatt, James, 1975-77 (Box 44, Folder 842)
    - MacNeice, Louis, 1952 Oct 28 (Box 44, Folder 843)
    - MacShane, Frank, 1959-79 (Box 44, Folder 844)
    - Madden, David, 1968-83 (Box 44, Folder 845)
    - Mademoiselle, 1944-79 (Box 44, Folder 846)
    - The Magazine, 1934-35 (Box 44, Folder 847)
    - Magic Lantern Books, 1978-80, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 848)
    - Maguire, John D., 1970-82 (Box 44, Folder 849)
    - Maine, University of, 1960-75 (Box 44, Folder 850)
    - Makowsky, Veronica, 1983-85 (Box 44, Folder 851)
    - Malamud, Bernard, 1963, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 852)
    - Malone, Dumas, 1952-74 (Box 44, Folder 853)
    - Malone, Michael, 1976-80 (Box 44, Folder 854)
    - Manfred, Frederick, 1954-88 (Box 44, Folder 855)
    - Mann, James, 1972-73 (Box 44, Folder 856)
    - Marquette University, 1948-61 (Box 44, Folder 857)
    - Marshall, Keith, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 858)
    - Martin, Jay, 1974-79, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 859)
    - Martz, Louis, 1953-85 (Box 44, Folder 860)
    - Maryland, University of, 1962-74 (Box 44, Folder 861)
    - Massachusetts, University of, 1953-79 (Box 44, Folder 862)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1961-70 (Box 44, Folder 863)
    - Mathiessen, F. O., 1943, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 864)
    - Matthews, Jack, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 865)
      See: Ohio University, Box 52, folder 1039
    - May, Carolyn, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 866)
    - Mayberry, George, 1949, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 867)
    - Mayewski, Pawel, 1958-66, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 868)
    - Mayo, E. L., 1963-68, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 869)
    - Mellen, Sydney, 1934-87 (Box 45, Folder 870-71)
    - Mellow, James, 1981, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 872)
    - Mellquist, Jerome, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 873)
    - Melville Society, 1972-74 (Box 45, Folder 874)
    - Mendenhall, Tom Mendenhall, Nellie, 1960-63 (Box 45, Folder 875)
    - Menner, Robert, 1942-50 (Box 45, Folder 876)
    - Merchant, Moelwyn, 1957-70 (Box 45, Folder 877)
    - Meredith, William, 1963-82 (Box 45, Folder 878-79)
    - Merton, Thomas, 1940 Sep 30 (Box 45, Folder 880)
    - Merwin, William S., 1954-86 (Box 45, Folder 881)
    - Meyers, Jeffrey, 1979-83 (Box 45, Folder 882)
    - Michener, James A., 1960-79 (Box 45, Folder 883)
    - Michigan, University of, 1946-72 (Box 45, Folder 884)
    - Middlebury College, 1950-66 (Box 45, Folder 885)
    - Milch, David, 1972-85, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 886)
    - Miles, Josephine, 1946, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 887)
    - Miller, Arthur, 1950 May 29 (Box 45, Folder 888)
    - Miller, Charles L., 1978-81, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 889)
    - Miller, Floyd, 1976-77 (Box 45, Folder 890)
    - Miller, Henry, 1945 Feb 7 (Box 45, Folder 891)
    - Miller, William, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 892)
    - Miller, William J., 1979-85 (Box 45, Folder 893)
    - Millgate, Michael, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 894)
    - Mims, Edwin
    - Minnesota, University of, 1942-85, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 895-96)
    - Minnesota, University of, Press, 1962-71 (Box 46, Folder 897-99)
    - Mississippi, University of, 1951-87 (Box 46, Folder 900)
      See also: Southern Literary Festival Association, Box 65, folder 1294
    - Missouri, University of, 1964-81, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 901)
    - Mizener, Arthur, 1945-74 (Box 46, Folder 902)
    - Modern Language Association, 1941-85 (Box 46, Folder 903)
    - Moe, Henry Allen
      See: Guggenheim Fellowship, Box 29, folder 565
    - Molzahn, Loretto, 1969, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 904)
    - Monk, Samuel Holt, 1946-80 (Box 46, Folder 905-07)
    - Montana State University, 1955-70 (Box 46, Folder 908)
    - Montgomery Seminar Council, 1971-78 (Box 46, Folder 909)
    - Montier, Albert, 1955-77, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 910)
    - Moore, Charles W., 953, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 911)
    - Moore, Geoffrey, 1953-67 (Box 46, Folder 912)
    - Moore, Henry T., 1945-65 (Box 46, Folder 913)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1945-60 (Box 46, Folder 914)
    - Moore, Merrill, 1933-57 (Box 46, Folder 915)
    - Moravia, Alberto Moravia, Elsa, 1948-58 (Box 46, Folder 916)
    - Morgan, Frederick, 1974-78, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 917)
    - Moritsu family, 1951-70 (Box 47, Folder 918)
    - Morley, Hilda (Wolpe), 1977-83 (Box 47, Folder 919)
    - Morris Harvey College Publications
      See: William Plumley, Box 55, folder 1100
    - Morris, Robert, 1970-79 (Box 47, Folder 920)
    - Morris, Willie, 1967-79 (Box 47, Folder 921)
    - Morris, Wright, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 922)
    - Morrow, Mark, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 923)
    - Moss, Charles Moss, Betty Lee, 1959-77 (Box 47, Folder 924)
    - Moss, Howard
      See: Box 137, folder 2493 (with draft of Chief Joseph of the Nez Perce ) and Box 226, folder 4081 (with "Inevitable Frontier")
    - Mostowski, Jan, 1977-86 (Box 47, Folder 925)
    - Mount Holyoke College, 1965-82 (Box 47, Folder 926)
    - Moyers, Bill, 1975 May 29 (Box 47, Folder 927)
    - Muller, Robert J., 1941-49 (Box 47, Folder 928)
    - Muenstenberger, Werner, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 929)
    - Murphy, Tim, 1970-76 (Box 47, Folder 930)
    - Murray, Henry A., 1969-88, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 931)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1963-71 (Box 47, Folder 932)
    - "N" general (Nagl-New S.), 1935-86 (Box 47, Folder 933-37)
    - "N" general (New York C-New York W), 1931-85 (Box 48, Folder 938-41)
    - Nahas, Alexander, 1977-79, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 942)
    - Nashville Tennessean, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 943)
    - Nason, John W., 1947-80 (Box 48, Folder 944)
    - Nassau Community College, 1965-68 (Box 48, Folder 945)
    - The Nation, 1942-77 (Box 48, Folder 946)
    - National Arts Club, 1962-74 (Box 48, Folder 947)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1964-65 (Box 48, Folder 948)
    - National Book Award, 1952-67 (Box 48, Folder 949)
    - National Book Award Committee, 1961-73 (Box 48, Folder 950-51)
    - Naional Book Committee, Inc., 1974 (Box 48, Folder 952)
    - National Broadcast Company, Inc. (NBC news), 1948-72 (Box 48, Folder 953)
    - National Citizens for Johnson and Humphrey, 1963-64 (Box 48, Folder 954)
    - National Council of Churches, 1954-64 (Box 48, Folder 955)
      See also: Marvin Halverson, Box 31, folder 587
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1968-87 (Box 48, Folder 956)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1973-85 (Box 48, Folder 957-58)
    - National Geographic Magazine, 1971-81 (Box 49, Folder 959)
    - National Institute of Arts and Letters, 1950-71 (Box 49, Folder 960-64)
    - National Jewish Hospital at Denver, 1961-66 (Box 49, Folder 965)
    - National Public Radio, 1979, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 966)
    - National Portrait Gallery, 1974-75 (Box 49, Folder 967)
    - National Retired Teachers' Association, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 968)
    - National Student Christian Federation, 1961-62 (Box 49, Folder 969)
    - Nebraska, University of, 1966-79 (Box 49, Folder 970)
    - Nelson, Robert J., 1961 (Box 49, Folder 971)
    - Nemerov, Howard, 1962-81, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 972)
    - Nevins, Allan, 1958-68 (Box 49, Folder 973)
    - Nevins, Barbara Nevins, Robert L., 1963-65 (Box 49, Folder 974)
    - New American Library, 1965-68 (Box 49, Folder 975)